const tasksSelect = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'You put things in this to carry them around.',
    variant1: 'bag',
    variant2: 'gloves',
    variant3: 'belt',
    variant4: 'earrings',
    correct: 'bag',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      'You wear this around your waist to hold your trousers up.',
    variant1: 'earrings',
    variant2: 'cap',
    variant3: 'bag',
    variant4: 'belt',
    correct: 'belt',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'You wear this on your head. It has a visor to protect your eyes from the sun.',
    variant1: 'cap',
    variant2: 'gloves',
    variant3: 'glasses',
    variant4: 'bag',
    correct: 'cap',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Jewelry for your ears.',
    variant1: 'scarf',
    variant2: 'gloves',
    variant3: 'cap',
    variant4: 'earrings',
    correct: 'earrings',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      'A piece of jewelry for your neck.',
    variant1: 'pocket',
    variant2: 'necklace',
    variant3: 'belt',
    variant4: 'scarf',
    correct: 'necklace',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Part of your trousers or jacket etc. where you can put things.',
    variant1: 'pocket',
    variant2: 'rucksack',
    variant3: 'scarf',
    variant4: 'cap',
    correct: 'pocket',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      'You wear these on your hands.',
    variant1: 'cap',
    variant2: 'scarf',
    variant3: 'pocket',
    variant4: 'gloves',
    correct: 'gloves',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'These help you to see!',
    variant1: 'glasses',
    variant2: 'gloves',
    variant3: 'scarf',
    variant4: 'pocket',
    correct: 'glasses',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'A bag that you wear on your back.',
    variant1: 'cap',
    variant2: 'gloves',
    variant3: 'rucksack',
    variant4: 'glasses',
    correct: 'rucksack',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'You wear this around your neck to keep warm.',
    variant1: 'scarf',
    variant2: 'rucksack',
    variant3: 'gloves',
    variant4: 'belt',
    correct: 'scarf',
  },
];

export default tasksSelect;
